https://saafmuseum.org.za/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
Home
About
Articles
The History of the South African Air Force (SAAF)
Articles
The History of the South African Air Force (SAAF)
Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy sets out how we use and protect any information that you give us when you use this website.We are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this Privacy Statement. From time to time we may change this policy by updating this page. You should regularly check this page to ensure that you are happy with any changes.
What We Collect
Log Files
When someone visits our website we collect standard internet log information and details of visitor behaviour patterns. We do this to find out things such as the number of visitors to the various parts of the site. We collect this information in a way which does not identify anyone. We do not make any attempt to find out the identities of those visiting our website using the data in the logs. We will not associate any log data gathered from this site with any personally identifying information from any source.
Comment and Enquiry Forms
Our website allows visitors to leave comments and contact us via an enquiry form. We collect the following information:
Contact details such as Name, Email, Web AddressIP AddressCommentEnquiry
We require this information for the following reasons:-
To improve our servicesEncourage visitor interaction and discussion on our websiteBe able to respond to visitor enquiriesWe may periodically send promotional email about new articles, events or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provide. You will have the opportunity to opt out of this at this time.
Cookies
Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer by websites that you visit. They are widely used in order to make websites work, or work more efficiently, as well as to provide information to the owners of the site. Cookies that are used by this website are necessary in order for us to provide and improve upon our value added products and services and to remain competitive. Cookies are not shared with any third parties.
We track website analytics using Google Analytics, and as a result cookies are used for this process. The cookies do not identify users nor associate your IP address with any personally identifiable information.
Google’s privacy policy is found here http://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html
Most web browsers allow some control of most cookies through the browser settings. To find out more about cookies, including how to see what cookies have been set and how to manage and delete them, visit www.allaboutcookies.org.
To opt out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites visit http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.
Third Party Cookies
Our website uses features of other websites that may leave a cookie. These are third-party cookies and we are unable to block or prevent them without removing the feature from our site. For information about those cookies you would need to check the originator’s website for their cookie policy. An example of a third party cookie is Facebook.  Facebooks privacy policy is set out here  http://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites, as such sites are not governed by this Privacy Statement. You should exercise caution and look at the Privacy Statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen. You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to us.If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
©  2020 South African Aviation Foundation Museum. Built using WordPress and the EmpowerWP Theme
